Guide to the International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers, Local 66 Records WAG.010
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series V: Finances, Membership Records, and General Files (Unprocessed), circa 1935-1984, 5
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Cash flow: Local 66 IFPTE Monthly reports (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Notes from various negotiating meetings: contract (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Tech Talk bulletin (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Engineers Outlook (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Correspondence: Receipts (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Meeting: Homdel Chapter: Local 66, Engineering and Professional Guild (May 17, 1984), May 1984 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Contract Negotiations: Homdel Chapter Local 66, 1983 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Proposed MOA, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Contract Negotiations: Homdel Chapter Local 66, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Contract Negotiations: Homdel Chapter Local 66, 1981 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Letters from members for merit review consideration (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: General membership meeting: Homdel Chapter Local 66 (August 3, 1983), Aug 1983 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Reproduction Technician / Junior Draftsman Proposal (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Maps/Route Diagrams (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Reclassifications/New Classifications, etc., 1970-1972 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Reclassifications/New Classifications, etc., 1969 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Reclassifications/New Classifications, etc., 1968 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Reclassifications/New Classifications, etc., 1967 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Correspondence: Initiated (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Addendum A: Classifications and Job Descriptions (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit review: 1st Meeting (January 13, 1976), Jan 1976 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit: Reclassification Requests, Jan 1975 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit review, Jan 1974 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit review information, 1968-1972 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit: Reclassification letters, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit: Reclassification letters, 1978 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit: Reclassification letters, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Pennwalt/SS White: Merit: Reclassification letters, 1980-1981 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Pennwalt/SS White:, 1964 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Pennwalt/SS White, 1960 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Pennwalt/SS White documents and files (Box 79)
  - Weekly reports of Business Manager J.L. Raimist, 1961-1962 (Box 80)
  - Shop files of Port Authority and R. Hoe (Box 80)
  - AFTE: National membership figures, 1952-1960 (Box 80)